Hello Hello Friends Welcome Now in this video we will
tell you how to take four wheeler insurance
which is necessary for every vehicle to have
insurance If there is
any damage to your vehicle or third party due to insurance
then whichever company you have taken
insurance from, that company will not fine you
You can go to your nearest CSC center and
take vehicle insurance of any company
Today I am going to take third party four wheeler insurance from CSC portal
A
customer is standing in front of me The customer
needs four wheeler insurance so I have to
make the insurance for him We are going to
take the insurance The name of the company is
ICICI Lombard But we are going to
take four wheeler third party insurance from this company
Log in to CSC portal
Insurance is showing here Click on it Scroll down here Click on
Motor
Third Party Click on it Motor Tk
Patti Post ICICI Lombard But here Click on click here
Connect with digital service Log in by entering ID password
ICICI Lombard But
official website has opened First when you
connect to CSC portal cell then My
Profile will be visible here Name of the customer will be visible
License number of the customer will be visible PAN  The number will be of the
company, the mobile number will be of the company, this
work will be of the company, this home number will be of the company, this email will be of the
company, the name of Delhi and the license
number will be there, everything else will be
of the company, it is showing on the right side, the
first one is commercial and the second one is third
party, so we are going to deduct insurance for an out of thirty four wheeler,
here it is showing
two wheeler TP, it means third
party, so today we are going to do car third party insurance,
click on it,
click on get, enter the registration number of the vehicle,
third party insurance of this registration has to be
deducted, copy it and
paste it here, click on get it all
details, the vehicle
[ __ ] RC details have been automatically detected, it is
showing the district, it is showing the vehicle registration
date, it is showing the state, it is
also showing the company of the vehicle, it is showing the vehicle
model number, the policy starts here, it
shows the country on which the policy is done, scroll down, the
engine oil number has been automated, the
chassis number has also been automatically detected,
body type, type of
manufacture, you have to select this,
if it is not selected then it will be
found in the RC book and take the RC book  It is there and you have to
find out the option description, do
not skip this, registration time individual
kaur prem, if it is in the name of any person then
individual has to be done, if the vehicle is in the
name of any company then corporate has to be
selected, similarly individual is
selected, already force personal
accident cover,
if you have already taken any insurance then keep it
ticked for this and if
you have not taken any interest earlier, if
you want that driver to also get the opportunity,
this tick has to be removed, DOES not have a
valid driving license, do
not select this, TPDDL third
party property dealer 6000, if you keep this then the
insurance company will
give you only 6000 for the 30th match and if you mark it no, then whatever the
third party damage is, the
insurance company will pay, so note it down,
still that insurance policy
details are shown here, if you already have a
policy
then you can select it, if you
do this then you have to enter the details of your insurance policy here,
so leave it
in no for now  Let it be, click on gate. The
total premium is being shown as Rs. 2828
normally. Vehicle details: Whoever can be
made normally, his name has to be entered. Nominee
relative has to be selected. Father is there, wife is there, wife is there,
whoever is there can be selected. No,
Minicoy has to be entered. Customer details have to be entered. Vehicle details have to be entered.
To enter the details,
click on it. Vehicle details have to be entered.
Title has to be selected. Mr. is mixed.
We have to take this in MS Word. This means we will
select Company Mr. and enter the name and
enter the date of birth and
take the Aadhar card. Fill the owner's details only after seeing it. It will be
better to
enter the address. Indian only address line 2 has to be
left. Length mark has to be also left.
Pin code has to be entered.
Select the city and state after entering the pin code or email ID.
Now you have to enter the mobile number. After entering the pin code,
select the option after selecting the pin code. Doing this,
CCTV has been detected. State has been
visited. Email ID has to be entered. Mobile
number has to be entered and after filling the details of N,
click on gate purpose. Bipolar is  You
have to click on it, you will get the payment option,
now the payment option has
come through CSC ID, you can make the payment by entering the CSC wallet PIN,
you will get the payment only,
you can print out the tips and show them to the customer, in the
same way you can remove two wheeler, four
wheeler third party insurance,
thanks for watching, if you liked the video then
like and subscribe to the channel, see you
in the next video